<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>AS197434</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AS197434</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.131.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 16:30:06 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 15:26:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>ASN19434 is a personal ASN which was established by me in August 1, 2023 with help from Cloudie and his partner Zappie Host LLC 🌐
The main reason started this journey was due some interesting routing decisions that some providers took&amp;hellip; Being independet and having his own control is awesome but comes with great responsibility, it&amp;rsquo;s quite complicated to learn all these things. The network is dedicated for education and learning purpose and is sometimes used in combination with my own services!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peering Policy</title>
      <link>/posts/peering-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 15:41:10 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/peering-policy/</guid>
      <description>So you decided to peer with AS197434? We want to do the process as seamless as possible, but in order to do achieve this you have to follow some basic rules. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, they aren&amp;rsquo;t that hard (only a security measure) 😉 Pssst: It also increases the peer count&amp;hellip;
Requirements / Rules In the possession of a RIPE assigned ASN and IPv6 prefix Have a valid and up to date PeeringDB profile Don&amp;rsquo;t under any circumstances point static or default routes towards us RPKI for validation would be useful, but RIR is required A valid RPKI would be useful for validation, valid RIR Entries are required Connections / Profile ASN Exchange Address AS47498 FogIXP 2001:7f8:ca:1:0:19:7434:1 AS36090 F4IX MCI 2602:fa3d:f4:1::ad AS211272 AXCIX Duesseldorf 2a0e:8f02:2260::34 AS202409 LocIX Frankfurt 2001:7f8:f2:e1:a5:19:7434:1185.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/posts/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 16:30:06 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/contact/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re living in a world where communication can be very easy. No matter if you need something special or just some help, reach us via E-Mail 📩!
Reason Address Questions or inquiries about peering with us peering@as197434.net Network or problem related matters noc@as197434.net Anything else we can help you with contact@as197434.net </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
